[Agent]Hank-Comm100 (Training): Dear Joe, thank you for contacting us! How may I help you?
[Visitor]Joe: Im not sure i had a tech question so I'm not sure this is the place
[Visitor]Joe: about android
[Agent]Hank-Comm100 (Training): Is your question with our Comm100 Livechat software?
[Visitor]Joe: not I don't think so sorry
[Visitor]Joe: Im an idiot
[Visitor]Joe: I saw android and chat in the same sentence
[Agent]Hank-Comm100 (Training): Hi, I’m trying to help but you might have come to a wrong website. This is Comm100, a live chat software provider. Our website is www.comm100.com. Is it possible that you confused us with another company?
[Visitor]Joe: well Im on a quest to find out if I can reprogram a android phone this is the wrong place sorry for wasting your time 
[Agent]Hank-Comm100 (Training): That's all right. Sorry for can't be more helpful at this time
