[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hello Burak, this is Norman with Comm100! How may I help you today?
[Visitor]Burak: hello norman
[Visitor]Burak: its me again 
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Yes
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: My Sup is back 
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: let me check with him
[Visitor]Burak: i'm waiting mate thank you
[Agent]: Agent Paul - Comm100 has joined the chat.
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hi there, this the correct credit card ending in 7019?
[Visitor]Burak: Hi paul that my virtual credit card 
[Visitor]Burak: my normal credit card not accepting system
[Visitor]Burak: that why i get banned
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: I am going to send you a secure credit card form to update the account.
[Agent]: Agent Paul - Comm100 has requested a form "Credit Card".
[Visitor]Burak: shall i move money to my normal credit card ?
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: if you could fill out that form and provide the credit card information I can update your account
[Visitor]Burak: ok let me move my money to normal credit card and try
[Visitor]: Visitor has submitted the form "Credit Card".
[Visitor]Burak: İs it ok Paul ?
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Thank you please give me a few moments to update the information
[Visitor]Burak: Well my name on card have turkish character, but i'm paying my bills with this detail on international sites
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Once again the charge has failed
[Visitor]Burak: i changed my detail again can you try again paul
[Visitor]Burak: thank you
[Visitor]Burak: because my system ends at 00:00 if i cant pay this my site support gonna stop
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Burak your site will not stop
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: If possible are you able to speak with your bank tomorrow?
[Visitor]Burak: İs there detail of error like "insifition funds" or something ?
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: sometimes bank's put holds on some transactions
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: for out of country
[Visitor]Burak: because i have 1,120 Turkish Lira which excanges $318 
[Visitor]Burak: when is my system gonna be suspended ?
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: I can put a note on your account, so you can get this issue resolved with the bank.
[Visitor]: Ticket S10000-T553268 is created. The chat transcript will be attached to this ticket after the transcript is saved by system.
[Visitor]Burak: thats mean my system not gonna stop in mid night ?
[Visitor]Burak: sorry for my bad english
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: What time is it right now in your area?
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: If your system stops we can reactivate until you can get this issue resolved with the credit card
[Visitor]Burak: +2 UTC which is 26/04/2016 22:28
[Visitor]Burak: Ok then i can leave office now i'll notice my workers
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: yes please, and let them know just to come into a chat and we can reactivate the account for them.
[Visitor]Burak: Ok Paul thank you for your helping
[Visitor]Burak: kind regards 
[Visitor]Burak: Have a nice day or night 
[Visitor]Burak: İ dont know where are you thats why =)
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: My pleasure, thank for using Comm100 and have good night! :)
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: We are in Vancouver Canada
[Visitor]Burak: Oww i'm in North Cyprus 
[Visitor]Burak: See you again
[Visitor]Burak: bye
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Bye
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
