[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Hi mamta, this is Terry with Comm100. How may I help you today?
[Visitor]mamta: Hello Terry, this is mamta. 
[Visitor]mamta: how are you? 
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Hello Mamta. I'm great. How about you? :)
[Visitor]mamta: I am fine
[Visitor]mamta: thank you for asking
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Cool. :)
[Visitor]mamta: Well terry, I have one query. 
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Sure go ahead.
[Visitor]mamta: In campaign, there an option for language.
[Visitor]mamta: Can I set multiple language at one time? 
[Visitor]mamta: Example: like there are 3 people who speaks Hindi, English and French. So is it possible to talk to them in their language at same time 
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Firstly can you please specify where you want to show different languages for different people?  
[Visitor]mamta: There is option to chose one. Therefore I am asking is it possible to chose multiple language? 
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: So if the visitor select the language Hindi, the chat will be routed to the Hindi language support agent? 
[Visitor]mamta: yes
[Visitor]mamta: but multiple languages together
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
