[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hello ak, this is Brian. How can I help you?
[Visitor]ak: i hv a doubt regarding jee
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Sorry what do you mean by " jee" ? 
[Visitor]ak: cn i get clg if my mark is 71 & cutoff is 81 in iit jee mains exam
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hi, you have reached the customer service department for Comm100 Live Chat. You are wrongly directed here. 
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
