[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hello Jimmy, this is Brian. How can I help you?
[Visitor]Jimmy: Brian , I received your message
[Visitor]Jimmy: i mean email
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Ok
[Visitor]Jimmy: i want to point out a thing
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Ok sure
[Visitor]Jimmy: For our VIP clients, there will be other groups with different initial letters.
[Visitor]Jimmy: so not just only AB
[Visitor]Jimmy: how do we overcome this problem?
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: You dont need to worry that as long as those initial letters wont be taken by other groups then it will be fine
[Visitor]Jimmy: we can add the conditions along the way?
[Visitor]Jimmy: like now there's new group  AX  , so the sytem will recognize it's vip clients?
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Yes just put ax under ab in the condition
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Pls dont worry for this.
[Visitor]Jimmy: so this is not SSO
[Visitor]Jimmy: it's just a method to work around
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: SSO wont work for you. First it cannot tell the difference of a VIP customer and second it will still show the chat button on the log in page
[Visitor]Jimmy: okay.
[Visitor]Jimmy: Brian , thank you so much...
[Visitor]Jimmy: I was wrong about you in the begining...
[Visitor]Jimmy: in the end ...you are the guy who tried your best to solve my problem
[Visitor]Jimmy: I really appreciate your effort
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: No problem Jimmy
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: We all want to help you out the soonest we can
[Visitor]Jimmy: thank you so much.  
[Visitor]Jimmy: thank you very much
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: You are very welcome 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: If there is still any question and you cannot find me on live chat you can always email me
[Visitor]Jimmy: okay sure
[Visitor]Jimmy: bye
[Visitor]Jimmy: :)
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Bye for now
[Agent]: Agent Brian - Comm100 has left the chat.
