[Agent]: Operator Brian - Comm100 has joined the chat.
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hello KENEAN MULUGETA, this is Brian. How can I help you?
[Visitor]KENEAN MULUGETA: i need to wright concern letter to my project manager can you send me samsample pls? 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hi, I’m trying to help but you might have come to a wrong website. This is Comm100, a live chat software provider. Our website is www.comm100.com. Is it possible that you confused us with another company?
[Visitor]KENEAN MULUGETA: oh sorry!
