[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hello Tifany , this is Brian. How can I help you?
[Visitor]Tifany : I was in  the webside of cinderella gowns and I wanted to now if the dress of little girls are in Stock  
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hi, I’m trying to help but you might have come to a wrong website. This is Comm100, a live chat software provider. 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: I think you were wrongly directed here 
[Visitor]Tifany : Ok 
[Visitor]Tifany : Sorry
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: No problem
