[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hello Indika, this is Brian. How can I help you?
[Visitor]Indika: Hello
[Visitor]Indika: Can you let me know if purchase Team license  can i use it for multiple web sites or only it's for one agent one web site?
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hi
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: It can be used on multiple websites
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: For the agent it will be just one
[Visitor]Indika: okie.. are you providing agents or i have to use my agents to support chats?
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: If you need more than one it needs to be purchased
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: No we dont provide agents
[Visitor]Indika: okie. do u support language translation?
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Yes we do .we have built-in google translator
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: But it is only available in our Business version and plus
[Visitor]Indika: okie
[Visitor]Indika: Thanks for the details
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: No problem
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
