[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hello Indika, this is Brian. How can I help you?
[Visitor]Indika: Hello   I need one more help
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: okay sure
[Visitor]Indika: when compare to LiveChatInc what are the features u guys provided
[Visitor]Indika: i'm sure u have done the comparison
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Is there anything you are looking for specifically? comparing with them we support chatbot  we support PCI we support audio video chat, all are not supported by them
[Visitor]Indika: great
[Visitor]Indika: I'm currently using LiveChatInc for few websites and one advantage is easy to configure  ,,, just have to copy paste the script
[Visitor]Indika: is it the same in comm100?
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Yes if you need the live chat to be identical for all sites  you can just copy and paste scripts
[Visitor]Indika: thats great,,,
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: If you need each website has a different chat, you can create different campaigns too. We support both ways
[Visitor]Indika: dynamic campaign are only available for enterprise? is it?
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: yes but to create different campaigns for different website does not need dynamic campaign. Team version supports it
[Visitor]Indika: okie,, what is dyanamic campaign?
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: let me get you an KB for this
[Visitor]Indika: Thanks
[Visitor]Indika: The chatbot u guys have launch,, is it available for Team?
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Yes it is supported but it needs extra purchase
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: For the dynamic campaign you can check here  https://www.comm100.com/livechat/features/different-websites-different-live-chats.aspx#dynamiccampaign
[Visitor]Indika: great,,, Thanks,, i started free tiral
[Visitor]Indika: Will contact if needed,, thanks again
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Okay great
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Thanks
[Visitor]Indika: sorry forget one thing to ask
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Ok
[Visitor]Indika: I have an internal knowledge base portal,,, i want to host it so my agents can quickly navigate KB
[Visitor]Indika: is there any integration u support for KB hosting
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Unfortunately we dont support KB hosting. We have a standalone product for the KB though
[Visitor]Indika: I'm sorry, i have it already hosted in my server,,, example, in LiveChatInc, i have the option of integrating that as an agent add on,, when a user comes from a site,,,, my KB portal will read user ID, identify which site user chat is coming and then open related KB ,, it was very helpful since otherwise agents have to navigate to a different site again for KB,, does your standalone product support that,, do u have  a KB link?
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Actually for our live chat, from the agent console, the agent will be able to read from which page the visitor is coming from or currently browsing. And he can directly click it to open the link.  
[Visitor]Indika: okie,, i guess i need to test the product,, for one license,, can i create multiple agent login's but i will get only one agent login at one time,, is it possible? 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Theoretically speaking, we sell the product as per agent logins, but we do have some policies which can facilitate for your case.  Our sales can talk to you for this, for the concurrent license details.  During the trial, you can create as many agents as you want. 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Is this the best email that we can reach you?   wimalasuriyaib*****gmail.com  I can get one of our sales agent to work with you for all of your questions during the trial and the best pricing we can do. 
[Visitor]Indika: yes,
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Thanks Indika :) 
[Visitor]Indika: Brian, I'm actually running a start up providing web site chat outsourcing ,,, we currently use LiveChatInc but language support,  voice etc are problematic so looking for other options for few clients
[Visitor]Indika: If you can pass that message to  your sales agent that would be great  our site is http://www.servicelive365.com/
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Yes I will, so basically, language support, and voice feature will be necessary correct? 
[Visitor]Indika: yes, also option of creating multiple agents using few license,,, i have 7 guys working but base on shifts only 2 ppl on desk any given time,, so with me, with 3 license we currently mange around 20+ sites,,, that way we can cut down our costs,, also what support u guys can give to a company like us, since what we going to is to buy your product and sell it to someone else with our agents :)
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Yes, I got that part.  Creating multiple agents using few license is applicable, I am sure our sales will work out a best solution for you.  For support, once the sale agent is assigned, he will be responsible for all of your questions and queries and quote, and we also provide 24. 7 customer service here on live chat.  You can totally rest assured.  
[Visitor]: Ticket S10000-T557510 is created. The chat transcript will be attached to this ticket after the transcript is saved by system.
[Visitor]Indika: Brian, thanks or your time, much appreciated,  i know i took lot of your time, so thanks again
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: You are very welcome Indika.  
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Our sales agent will reach out to you via email very soon,  if you have any questions during the trial,  you can feel free to ask him 
[Visitor]Indika: sure will do,,, if not i will buzz here,,, hope you guys are 24x7
[Visitor]Indika: ;)
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Of course, no problem,  we are definitely here 24 *7 
