[Agent]Hank-Comm100 (Training): Dear Sonvver, thank you for contacting us! How may I help you?
[Visitor]Sonvver: What kind of help do you provide?
[Agent]Hank-Comm100 (Training): LiveChat configuration , features problem solving 
[Visitor]Sonvver: Okay you are here to help new agent 
[Agent]Hank-Comm100 (Training): I am not that senior, we work as team
[Visitor]Sonvver: Okay no problem
[Visitor]Sonvver: I need some help regarding live chat 
[Visitor]Sonvver: Can you send me all script that i can use them as a live chat agent
[Agent]Hank-Comm100 (Training): That's not normal process. You can register as our trial user and then get chat button code and download desktop/mobile APP.
[Visitor]Sonvver: How i register?
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
