[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hi raj, thank you for contacting Comm100. How can I help you?
[Visitor]raj: hi
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hello

[Visitor]raj: hi
[Visitor]raj: do you offer on premise installation?
[Visitor]raj: hi
[Visitor]raj: are you there?
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hi Raj, we do offer on premise installation.
[Visitor]raj: can you give me some idea how much it will cost for 10 agents 
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: If you like I can have a sales representative get in contact with.
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: May I please get your contact information.
[Visitor]: Ticket S10000-T557684 is created. The chat transcript will be attached to this ticket after the transcript is saved by system.
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hi Raj are you still with me?
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hi, I haven't got any reply from you. It seems that you’re not available at the moment. I am going to leave this chat now. If you have any other questions, please feel free to try us again anytime. Bye for now and have a great day!
[Agent]: Operator Paul - Comm100 has left the chat.
