[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hello Flo Childerhose, this is Norman with Comm100! How may I help you today?
[Visitor]Flo Childerhose: My husbands emails to me  are going into my junk mail.  All my other emails go into my inbox.  Why is that?
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: You will have to accept his email as a known email address
[Visitor]Flo Childerhose: what are the steps to do that
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: You will have to check that with your email provider
[Visitor]Flo Childerhose: Thank you Norman
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: My Pleasure!
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Thank you for contacting Comm 100 today!
Have a great day ahead!
