[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hello Jenn, this is Norman with Comm100! How may I help you today?
[Visitor]Jenn: Hi Norman, our time stamp is accurate within chats but I notice that a chat from last night is now showing a different time in the transcript than the time the chat took place.
[Visitor]Jenn: I can't find time zone in the settings and want to double check it.
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Sorry for the delayed reply
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: You will have to check the time zone settings in "My Account" on the top right hand corner on your dashboard
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: From "My Account" you will have to go to the operator and check which operator took that chat and then se the time zone
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Also please check the time zone for your main system
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Was this of any help ?
[Visitor]Jenn: Sorry - I will check this out now.
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Sure please go ahead
[Visitor]Jenn: From my account, I don't see a prompt to select an operator
[Visitor]Jenn: Nevermind, found it
[Visitor]Jenn: Ok, it's set to "automatically use the time zone of my machine" which is EST 
[Visitor]Jenn: Changing it to EST helps thanks
[Visitor]Jenn: What do you mean by please check the time zone for the main system?
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: I meant your computer and the timezone on the user
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: So you have that covered already 
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: It should be good now
[Visitor]Jenn: Ok thanks for your help
[Visitor]: The transcript will be sent to "jcarroll*****nationaleatingdisorders.org".
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
