[Agent]: Operator Terry - Comm100 has joined the chat.
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Hi Herve, this is Terry with Comm100. How may I help you today?
[Visitor]Herve: HI there
[Visitor]Herve: I am looking for a service like yours for our society and I have couple of questions I would like your answer
[Visitor]Herve: first where is your company located? 
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Hi Herve, thanks  for contacting us. I would like to forward your request to our sales team to better help you. 
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: We are  located in Vancouver Canada. Can I have your questions and send it to our sale team? 
[Visitor]Herve: would like to know if you hold any of your server in Europe?
[Visitor]Herve: and what also what are the cost ?
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Thanks for your questions, Our enterprise Sales rep. will be in touch with about this. May I have your best email address or phone number to reach you at?
[Visitor]Herve: herve.songue*****familybsoc.co.uk
[Visitor]Herve: 01372****5415
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Thanks, May I know how many live chat agents you are going to start with?
[Visitor]Herve: possibly 5 as a start
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: May I have your website address to better understand your business? 
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: It will be the website where you are going to install the live chat. 
[Visitor]Herve: http://familybuildingsociety.co.uk/
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Thanks so much for the info. That's pretty much the info I need for now. Our sales rep. will be in touch with you soon. 
[Visitor]: Ticket S10000-T557643 is created. The chat transcript will be attached to this ticket after the transcript is saved by system.
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Anything else I can help you at this moment? 
[Visitor]Herve: o that will do 
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Okay. 
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Thanks for your interest and have a good one, Herve. 
[Visitor]Herve: Thanks again
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
