[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Hi jessica, this is Terry with Comm100. How may I help you today?
[Visitor]jessica: i just wanted some advice im creating e-shots for my company and going to be sending them out to customers what is the limit i should send so they dont go into spam folders?
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Are you using  Email marketing service?
[Visitor]jessica: yeah mail chimp
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: May I have your account email address with us?
[Visitor]jessica: my email is jessica.ohara*****adnetworksolutions.co.uk
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Actually I cannot locate an account with this email address in our system.  But if you are planning to use our Email Marketing service, you need to make sure all your customer contacts are opt-in. 
[Visitor]jessica: i am not doing it through your system sorry i just wanted some advice on how many i should send so that it doesnt go into the spam accounts
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Alright, in that case, you have to contact your service provider for more info. 
[Visitor]jessica: okay thanks
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: No problem. Bye for now. 
[Agent]: Agent Terry - Comm100 has left the chat.
