[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Hi Andrew E, this is Terry with Comm100. How may I help you today?
[Visitor]Andrew E: Hello again Terry. I was able to reset my password, but it says that the password is incorrect when I try to login with it.
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: As you are with Uk2 group, and you are hosted on dedicated server, please make sure you login with link: 
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: https://livechat.uk2group.com/AdminManage/Login.aspx?
