[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hello Barbara, this is Norman with Comm100! How may I help you today?
[Visitor]Barbara: Can you tell me how long it is taking to receive a Cuban visa?
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hi, I’m trying to help but you might have come to a wrong website. This is Comm100, a live chat software provider. Our website is www.comm100.com. Is it possible that you confused us with another company?
[Visitor]Barbara: sorry
[Agent]: Operator Norman - Comm100 has left the chat.
