[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hello Leo, this is Norman with Comm100! How may I help you today?
[Visitor]Leo: Norman my apologies I am leaving for a week and need this solved before I go
[Visitor]Leo: Is it possible for you to go to my public page and send a chat and see what appears there? Is not disappearing and cannot find where did I programmed this
[Visitor]Leo: http://www1.toronto.ca/wps/portal/contentonly?vgnextoid=d7f87dbbfd510410VgnVCM10000071d60f89RCRD
[Visitor]Leo: open a chat, put test on the last line so i know is you, read what it appears while you wait for my answer, I cannot find it so I can erase it
[Visitor]Leo: Are you there>?
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: i am there
[Visitor]Leo: yes but what I wanted you to see if the message that appears while you wait for my answer underneath the black letters, so on gray
[Visitor]Leo: send me another one, sorry
[Visitor]Leo: Thank you for visiting the AIDS & Sexual Health eChat. All our counselors are busy at the moment. Your chat is important to us and we will be with you as soon as possible.
 
Alternatively, you may call 1-800-668-2437 to talk with one of our phone counselors. 
 
When you chat, there will be a transcript that you can print at any time by selecting the printer icon below.
Please wait for a site agent to respond...
If you do not want to wait, please click here to leave us a message.
[Visitor]Leo: That's the full message, but I need to take away the option to click here to leave us a message, we don't want messages from the public when we're away. 
[Visitor]Leo: so the last paragraph
[Agent]ae26bd6354024061a016b3927d6e97fe.png: Agent Norman - Comm100 has sent a file: ae26bd6354024061a016b3927d6e97fe.png
[Visitor]Leo: O got it thanks Norman have a good evening
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: great
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Thank you for contacting Comm 100 today!
Have a great day ahead!
[Agent]: Agent Norman - Comm100 has left the chat.
