[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hello Wasif Saleheen, this is Norman with Comm100! How may I help you today?
[Visitor]Wasif Saleheen: i had a free account with comm100 with email billing*****mahvishgroup.com
[Visitor]Wasif Saleheen: can i reactivate that?
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: when did you use it last time ?
[Visitor]Wasif Saleheen: i guess a month back
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: sorry we have closed all the free accounts which were not in use
[Visitor]Wasif Saleheen: so i gotta create a new one?
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
