[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hello addison adler, this is Norman with Comm100! How may I help you today?
[Visitor]addison adler: i am currently using Zopim chat services and was thinking to switch to a new vendor. we have around 20-25 agents for whom we require the services.what sort of a cost we are talking about?
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: it will be in your best interest to talk to our solutions specialist. we are here for support.
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: shall i create a ticket for you ? so that our specialist can contact you ?
[Visitor]addison adler: Can you connect me to him?
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: sure
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: what is your best email address to contact ?
[Visitor]addison adler: PLease connect me to him
[Visitor]addison adler: We have to make the decision today
[Visitor]addison adler: addison.adler*****logoscientist.com, zach*****logoscientist.com
[Visitor]: Ticket S10000-T556455 is created. The chat transcript will be attached to this ticket after the transcript is saved by system.
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: i have created a ticket for this. our team will contact you as soon as possible.
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: meanwhile you can learn all about comm100 on our website blog https://www.comm100.com/blog/
[Visitor]addison adler: Can you connect me to your guy here on chat?
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: no i am sorry team here is only for technical support.
[Visitor]addison adler: Is he going to contact me via email?
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: i would love to help you but it will be in your best interest if you talk to our solutions specialist.
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: yes they will contact you via email.
[Visitor]addison adler: Okay thanks
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Thank you for contacting Comm 100 today!
Have a great day ahead!
[Agent]: Operator Norman - Comm100 has left the chat.
