[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hello naimhamdard, this is Brian. How can I help you?
[Visitor]naimhamdard: Hi, Brian. can you help with live chat agent interview questions :)
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Yes sure
[Visitor]naimhamdard: What are the most commonly asked questions in an interview for this position
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Oh sorry Naimhamdard you have reached the customer service department of Comm100, we only deal with the questions for the software only here.
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
