[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hello Asmita, this is Norman with Comm100! How may I help you today?
[Visitor]Asmita: Hi 
[Visitor]Asmita: How do i deal with customera who are irate because of product compatibility issue
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hi, I’m trying to help but you might have come to a wrong website. This is Comm100, a live chat software provider. Our website is www.comm100.com. Is it possible that you confused us with another company?
