[Visitor]Stephanie: Hi, Chatbot. 
[Visitor]Stephanie: Can you verify when Veridian's next billing date is? 
[Visitor]Stephanie: Currently it shows 04/28/16.
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hello Stephanie, this is Norman with Comm100! How may I help you today?
[Visitor]Stephanie: Can you verify Veridian's next billing date? 
[Visitor]Stephanie: It currently says 04/28/16.
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Sure let me try to check that for you
[Visitor]Stephanie: We also added 3 additional operators today, can you provide me the cost per operator added. Is this per month or per year? 
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Stephanie as you are an on premise account and your account manager is Rob, I will have to forward this to him to reply back to you
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Will it be alright if Rob can email you the details?
[Visitor]Stephanie: Yes, you sure can. 
[Visitor]: Ticket S10000-T560145 is created. The chat transcript will be attached to this ticket after the transcript is saved by system.
[Visitor]Stephanie: Stephanieem*****Veridiancu.org
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: What would be the best email to reach out to you?
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Thank you!
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: I will get this information as soon as possible
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Is there anything else I can assist you with at this time?
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Thank you for contacting Comm 100 today!
Have a great day ahead!
[Agent]: Agent Norman - Comm100 has left the chat.
