[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hi sam, thank you for contacting Comm100. How can I help you?
[Visitor]sam: What is this site all about?
[Visitor]sam: Can you please guide me.
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Comm100 Live Chat is the enterprise-grade live chat software for website. It allows your website visitors to chat live with your customer support and sales representatives and have their questions answered instantly. Here is the details page: https://www.comm100.com/livechat/knowledgebase/what-is-comm100-live-chat-about.html
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Samu was there anything else that I could help you with today?
