[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hello Belal Barkati, this is Brian. How can I help you?
[Visitor]Belal Barkati: assalamo alaikum w.r w.b
[Visitor]Belal Barkati: hazrat mujhe almdih ul nabawi ki urdu sharah chahye 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hi, I’m trying to help but you might have come to a wrong website. This is Comm100, a live chat software provider. Our website is www.comm100.com. Is it possible that you confused us with another company?
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
