[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hello ginadel, this is Norman with Comm100! How may I help you today?
[Visitor]ginadel: hi
[Visitor]ginadel: any suggestion on how we can empathize to a payment that was not received for almost 3 weeks now?
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hi, I’m trying to help but you might have come to a wrong website. This is Comm100, a live chat software provider. Our website is www.comm100.com. Is it possible that you confused us with another company?
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
