[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hello Zoya, this is Brian. How can I help you?
[Visitor]Zoya: Are your services 24/7 or do you operate within specific working hours
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Our live chat support here will be 24* 7 
[Visitor]Zoya: And does your software use chat tags?
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: We support the wrap-up function, with which you can categorize the chat with tags. 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Zoya, are you looking for adding a live chat to your website? 
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
