[Visitor]jeremy: hi, i cant get the comms chat to auto start when i turn on the pc, i have put a tick in the box in "other" setting
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hello jeremy, this is Brian. How can I help you?
[Visitor]jeremy: hi, i cant get the comms chat to auto start when i turn on the pc, i have put a tick in the box in "other" setting
[Agent]snipaste20170724_072506.png: Agent Brian - Comm100 has sent a file: snipaste20170724_072506.png
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hi Jeremy, you mean here right? 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Already checked off? 
[Visitor]jeremy: theres a tick in the box
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Okay, please hold on 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hi Jeremy, will you please try this way?   Please run this command : msconfig in your computer,  and then you will get the task manager box,  please click : startup.   and in the status column, please check if the Comm100live chat is in : enabled status.  If not, please enable it first, and restart your computer. 
[Agent]snipaste20170724_073543.png: Agent Brian - Comm100 has sent a file: snipaste20170724_073543.png
[Visitor]jeremy: IM BACK SOORY
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: It is okay, please check my above message 
[Visitor]jeremy: I LOOKED THERE, COMM100 ISNT IN THE LIST
[Visitor]jeremy: theres an option to run a new task
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: If it is not in the list, it should be that the auto start is not set up correct. 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Can you please confirm again, in the others part, the auto startup is ticked? 
[Visitor]jeremy: YES IT IS
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Can you please take a screenshot image for your current task manager? 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Like the one I sent over above? 
[Visitor]zz.jpg: The visitor has sent a file: zz.jpg
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Thanks one moment please 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hi Jeremy, thanks a lot for your patience,  here will be the way on how to add it to your startup list,  please run this command : regedit  and then please open the file with this path: HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SOFTWARE\Microsoft\Windows\CurrentVersion\Run   and in the run file, please name a new key , and for the data column , please enter your current comm100 live chat path there, and then save it, it will be done. 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hi, I haven't got any reply from you. It seems that you’re not available at the moment. I am going to leave this chat now. If you have any other questions, please feel free to try us again anytime. Bye for now and have a great day!
[Agent]: Agent Brian - Comm100 has left the chat.
