[Visitor]Arthur: I have done a order of frozen bait but Carnt check out to pay
[Visitor]Arthur: OK
[Visitor]Arthur: Do u have a phone number
[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: Hi Arthur, this is Mellisa with Comm100. How may I help you today?
[Visitor]Arthur: I have tried to order some frozen pike bait but Carnt check out my bill was 20 quid
[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: I’m trying to help but you might have come to a wrong website. This is Comm100, a Canadian based customer service software company. Our website is www.comm100.com.
