[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hi ibra el , thank you for contacting Comm100. How can I help you?
[Visitor]ibra el : hello; i need some help for my ips server  ;iam warming up my ips since 14 days ago but none of them is going to the inbox folder so what can i do for that plz
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hi, I’m trying to help but you might have come to a wrong website. This is Comm100, a live chat software provider. Our website is www.comm100.com. Is it possible that you confused us with another company?
[Visitor]ibra el : ok im sry
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
