[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hi Chinmoy Maji , thank you for contacting Comm100. How can I help you?
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hello, how are you today?
[Visitor]Chinmoy Maji : I am Chinmoy 
[Visitor]Chinmoy Maji : Tumi ke 
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hi Chinmoy, I’m trying to help but you might have come to a wrong website. This is Comm100, a live chat software provider. Our website is www.comm100.com. Is it possible that you confused us with another company?
[Visitor]Chinmoy Maji : Why are you 
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: We are a software company from Vancouver Canada
