[Visitor]Lori: im am trying to integrate with zendesk but comm100 is not accepting my credentials
[Visitor]Lori: I followed that tutorial and am still having problems
[Agent]: Agent Mellisa -Comm100 has joined the chat.
[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: Hi Lori, this is Mellisa with Comm100. How may I help you today?
[Visitor]Lori: Hi! I am trying to enter in my zendeks information to integrate with comm100
[Visitor]Lori: and i have tried several administrator accounts but comm100 keeps rejecting my credentials for integration
[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: Did you receive any error message?
[Visitor]Lori: Error saving zendesk integration
Your site name, user name or password may be wrong. Please check.
[Visitor]Lori: i am VERY confident I am entering the correct information.
[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: Have you enabled the Zendesk API?
[Visitor]Lori: yes
[Visitor]Lori: we use the zendesk API for other integrations.
[Visitor]Lori: does the password in comm100 need to be the API key to zendesk rather than a zendesk admin account username and password?
[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: The Zendesk's account login info will work.
[Agent]Zendesk API.jpg: Agent Mellisa -Comm100 has sent a file: Zendesk API.jpg
[Visitor]Lori: ah ha
[Visitor]Lori: let me check that. one momebnt
[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: Can you please check this setting on your Zendesk backend
[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: Sure, take your time
[Visitor]Lori: that was it!
[Visitor]Lori: we're integrated. thank you so much!
[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: You are welcome. :)
[Visitor]Lori: thats all i needed today. thank you very much. have a nice tuesday :) happy august 1st
[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: Thanks, you too!
[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: See you
