[Agent]Prit - Comm100: Hi Eric, thank you for contacting Comm100. How can I help you?
[Visitor]Eric: I'm back - getting reports from our agents that the wrap ups were intermittent today.  If they had more than one chat open at a time, only one of them would have the new categories.  Is that because they weren't under "category"?
[Agent]Prit - Comm100: Yes that could be the issue, in this case you will need to add them from the actual chat transcript in the history section.
[Agent]Prit - Comm100: Also your agents might need to log out and log back in to see the new changes in the wrap up section.
[Visitor]Eric: OK.  thanks 
[Agent]Prit - Comm100: You're welcome, was there any other item I could help you with?
