[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hello Ana Ross, this is Norman with Comm100! How may I help you today?
[Visitor]Ana Ross: hi
[Visitor]Ana Ross: there?
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: How may I assist you today?
[Visitor]Ana Ross: I have just updated my card details please take your payment accordingly
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Sure! please stay with me for a minute while I try to get it processed
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Ana it will take around an hour to settle the payment on your account
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: will that work for you
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: I have notified the relevant department and they will process it soon
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: May I have your best contact email so that I can send the confirmation?
[Visitor]: Ticket S10000-T547950 is created. The chat transcript will be attached to this ticket after the transcript is saved by system.
[Visitor]Ana Ross: thansk
