[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Hi Muhammad Naeem, this is Terry with Comm100. How may I help you today?
[Visitor]Muhammad Naeem: How can I chat with girlfriends
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Hi, I’m trying to help but you might have come to a wrong website. This is Comm100, a live chat software provider. Our website is www.comm100.com. 
[Visitor]Muhammad Naeem: Please tell me the sources & methods
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: You are in wrong place. Bye for now.
[Visitor]Muhammad Naeem: What are the objectives of your website
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: We provide live chat software for your website so you can chat with your customers. 
[Agent]: Agent Terry - Comm100 has left the chat.
