[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hi Gianni, thank you for contacting Comm100. How can I help you?
[Visitor]Gianni: Hi Paul, do you have an update for me?
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hi Gianni, the team is building your enterprise trial account and will try to bring over your campaigns
[Visitor]Gianni: You think we will have it today, your day?
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: I will see what I can do to help speed up the process.
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Gianni thanks for waiting, I found out from the team that to import the items into the enterprise trial will take a few days,  instead our team is going to build the enterprise trial using all the same settings which you have in the business trial.
[Visitor]Gianni: That would be great. If I had known this would be needed, it would have been better to have started in the business trial.
[Visitor]Gianni: Question: if they make new campaigns, will I need to update the code on my websites?
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Yes you will have to update the codes on the site. They will create the new trial using the settings and keep your current trial open as well. 
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Once you are ready to switch over all you will need to do is update the code on the sites.
[Visitor]Gianni: ok, perfect
[Visitor]Gianni: What about the time remaining for the trial?
[Visitor]Gianni: Can you extend enough so we can test as much as needed?
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Absolutely
[Visitor]Gianni: Did the team let you know when I can expect the trial to be ready? Just for planning purposes on my side
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hopefully it should be ready to go by end of day today.
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: We will send you the credentials as soon as it is online.
[Visitor]Gianni: sounds good. Thanks for the help
[Visitor]Gianni: bye
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: My pleasure, have a great evening! 
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Bye
[Agent]: Agent Paul - Comm100 has left the chat.
