[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hi NPCE  , thank you for contacting Comm100. How can I help you?
[Visitor]NPCE  : Can you please make sure my emails g out now? I dont want to be waiting for hours 
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hi There, please give me a moment to pull up your account.
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Thank you for waiting, it shows the queue is all clear, have you sent out the email?
[Visitor]NPCE  : yes i did
[Visitor]NPCE  : but sometimes your q takes 5 hours and when customers call me back Im closed 
[Visitor]NPCE  : still says sending its been about 15 minutes
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: How many emails are you sending out at the moment?
[Visitor]NPCE  : 3300
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: On your end is it still saying sending?
