[Visitor]Paco: Hi, my name is Paco and I wonder if you sell electroacustics guitars
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hello Paco, this is Norman with Comm100! How may I help you today?
[Visitor]Paco: Hi, my name is Paco and I wonder if you sell electroacustics guitars
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hi, I’m trying to help but you might have come to a wrong website. This is Comm100, a live chat software provider. Our website is www.comm100.com. Is it possible that you confused us with another company?
[Visitor]Paco: Sorry
[Visitor]Paco: Yes I may but thanks thanks for your atention
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: no problem :)
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: good bye
[Agent]: Agent Norman - Comm100 has left the chat.
