[Agent]: Agent Brian - Comm100 has joined the chat.
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hello vladimir_v_m80, this is Brian. How can I help you?
[Visitor]vladimir_v_m80: Please check A2017072*********5938, it should be back to your warehouse
[Visitor]: The credit card number in the message has been masked for privacy.
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hi, I’m trying to help but you might have come to a wrong website. This is Comm100, a live chat software provider. Our website is www.comm100.com. Is it possible that you confused us with another company?
[Visitor]vladimir_v_m80: A2017072*********5938
[Visitor]: The credit card number in the message has been masked for privacy.
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Sorry but you are wrongly directed. 
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
