[Visitor]monitoring user: Request an extension to the trial
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hello monitoring user, this is Norman with Comm100! How may I help you today?
[Visitor]monitoring user: Hi, I am requesting an extension of the trial version for comm 100. We are wanting to demo it to the business this week as well as I need additional time to test the Javascript functionality.
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Sure I can forward your request to your accounts manager and he will be able to grant you the extension 
[Visitor]: Ticket S10000-T561190 is created. The chat transcript will be attached to this ticket after the transcript is saved by system.
[Visitor]monitoring user: We have been dealing with Prit..
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Yes I can see that on our system that Prit is your accounts manager
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: How many days do you want the trial to be extended?
[Visitor]monitoring user: Also I am also wanting to followup with him reguarding the proposal document and feedback from your engineers
[Visitor]monitoring user: We are requesting to have the trial extended by another 30 days please.
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Alright I will pass this information out to Prit and he will get in touch with you at earliest
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: May I have your best contact number please, so that I can expedite this
[Visitor]monitoring user: he can reach me on mzanatta*****auscript.com.au. Also can he please cc mcuff*****auscript.com.au
[Visitor]monitoring user: ideally he can reach me on my mobile +614*****76041
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Perfect! Thank you!
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: I have forwarded your message to Prit
[Visitor]monitoring user: Thankyou
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Is there anything else you would like to add in?
[Visitor]monitoring user: Just the followup re the javascript and the proposal
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hi, I just spoke to Prit and he said that he will reach out at earliest
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: I will now end this session 
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Thank you for contacting Comm 100 today!
Have a great day ahead!
[Agent]: Agent Norman - Comm100 has left the chat.
