[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hi Muhammad Usman  , thank you for contacting Comm100. How can I help you?
[Visitor]Muhammad Usman  : Hi Dear
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hello, how are you today?
[Visitor]Muhammad Usman  : I'm fine.
[Visitor]Muhammad Usman  : Thanks
[Visitor]Muhammad Usman  : And you
[Visitor]Muhammad Usman  : Can you briefly describe your service?
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Comm100 Live Chat is the enterprise-grade live chat software for website. It supports both hosted and on-premises deployments. Comm100 live chat software allows your website visitors to chat live with your customer support and sales representatives and have their questions answered instantly.

Comm100 live chat software promotes your sales, reduces operating costs and increases your customer satisfaction.

Comm100 Live Chat is powerful yet easy to use. It only takes you a few minutes to get started.
[Visitor]Muhammad Usman  : How to download your application?
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: I see that you have setup a  trial account all you will need to do is to sign into www.comm100.com
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: https://www.comm100.com/livechat/knowledgebase/get-started-with-comm100-live-chat.html
