[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Hi Tom, this is Terry with Comm100. How may I help you today?
[Visitor]Tom: Hey Terry. I was just wondering if you had any reports coming in over the past week or days of the windows chat program crashing or freezing?
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Hi Tom
[Visitor]Tom: At first it was just a few operators here and there where the chat program became unresponsive, since a few days it seems to be affecting more and more agents.
[Visitor]Tom: The browser chat program works just fine, it is only the windows program that has issues.
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Do you mean the Desktop App is crashing or freezing, right?
[Visitor]Tom: correct
[Visitor]Tom: It becomes un-responsive and then windows displays the program stopped working
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: No, we haven't got any report regarding this.  So it this occur to all of your agents now?
[Visitor]Tom: it affects over 50% of agents during the course of a shift.
[Visitor]Tom: As it seems at random and we have not been able to narrow down the cause.
[Visitor]Tom: It does not affect the agents at the same time, rather at random times 1 agent at a time.
[Visitor]Tom: today at our 2pm shift start, 7 agents had the shoftware crash within the first 30 minutes of their shift
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Can you please help collect the computer info of the agent who had this problem? Like OS, live chat version, adobe air version? 
[Visitor]Tom: we are all running the same OS, adobe air and chat version. 
[Visitor]Tom: chat version 8.1.0, adobe air V22
[Visitor]Tom: just getting you the windows version details
[Visitor]Tom: FYI, but own chat program just crashed also while i was chatting with you. I have not used or touched it since i started chatting with you. It was idle on my 2nd screen/monitor
[Visitor]Tom: we are running Windows 7 Enterprise SP1
[Visitor]Tom: here the screenshots of the crash
[Visitor]crash1.JPG: The visitor has sent a file: crash1.JPG
[Visitor]crash2-program greyed out.JPG: The visitor has sent a file: crash2-program greyed out.JPG
[Visitor]crash3.JPG: The visitor has sent a file: crash3.JPG
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: For this crash, will it be recovered soon?
[Visitor]Tom: no, it does not recover. we need to force close the program and restart it
[Visitor]Tom: we tried waiting and it does not recover by itself
[Visitor]Tom: We had a similar issue when we first switched to Comm100 in september last year, which was due to adobe air V23, so we downgraded to V22 and the problem was resolved until it started again a few weeks ago and is getting worse now.
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Ok, let me forward this to our tech team. If we need any further info, I will let you know. 
[Visitor]Tom: Thank you.
[Visitor]Tom: Can you create me a ticket also please for reference?
[Visitor]: Ticket S10000-T548558 is created. The chat transcript will be attached to this ticket after the transcript is saved by system.
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Sure.
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Do you all run adobe air version 22 now?
[Visitor]Tom: yeah
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: OK. Thanks. Will you update you soon. 
[Visitor]Tom: thank you
[Visitor]: The transcript will be sent to "tseelbach*****itsmanagement.net".
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: No problem! Have a good one, Tom. 
[Visitor]Tom: Thanks
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Bye for now.
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
