[Agent]Prit - Comm100: Hi Dave, thank you for contacting Comm100. How can I help you?
[Visitor]Dave: I'm currently in the Live Chat Agent Console and we have a couple of visitors that we have chatted with.  For someone reason their still show up in our system under the total time column.  I was wondering how we can boot them off so that they don' continue to appear there.  One is from Jan 30th.
[Agent]Prit - Comm100: Dave would it be possible to send a screen shot?
[Visitor]Dave: Yes.
[Agent]Prit - Comm100: Thank you
[Visitor]Untitled.png: The visitor has sent a file: Untitled.png
[Agent]Prit - Comm100: Dave I am also going to create a ticket for this issue and get my technical team to see what the cause is
[Visitor]: Ticket S10000-T548469 is created. The chat transcript will be attached to this ticket after the transcript is saved by system.
[Agent]Prit - Comm100: May I please get url where this chat is hosted?
[Visitor]: The transcript will be sent to "david.a.mackley*****multco.us".
[Visitor]Dave: Multco.us
[Agent]Prit - Comm100: Thank you
[Visitor]Dave: No, thank you!
[Visitor]Dave: Have a good day!
[Agent]Prit - Comm100: Thank you for stopping by Comm100 and enjoy the rest of your day!
[Agent]Prit - Comm100: Bye for now
[Agent]: Agent Prit - Comm100 has left the chat.
