[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hello Greg Coleman, this is Norman with Comm100! How may I help you today?
[Visitor]Greg Coleman: Hi Norman, I have another question, apologies.
[Visitor]Greg Coleman: Can a chatbot redirect chats to specific agents based on the query ?
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: No sir, that is under development at the moment and might get released in the future version
[Visitor]Greg Coleman: can the chatbot determine language and choose answer in specific language ?
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Yes that is available
[Visitor]Greg Coleman: great - does the chatbot use machine learning ?
[Visitor]Greg Coleman: or is all of the information manually fed into the system ?
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: It uses machine learning as far as I am aware of
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: How ever if you prefer I can have a solutions specialist reach out to you with further details?
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Are we still connected?
[Agent]: Operator Norman - Comm100 has left the chat.
