[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Hi sravani deepu, this is Terry with Comm100. How may I help you today?
[Visitor]sravani deepu: Actually i want some help from you
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: How can I help you?
[Visitor]sravani deepu: I attended an interview for call center yesterday.. but i am rejected in it
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Hi, I’m trying to help but you might have come to a wrong website. This is Comm100, a live chat software provider. Our website is www.comm100.com. Is it possible that you confused us with another company?
[Visitor]sravani deepu: I want some scenarios about customer servoce through email
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: https://www.comm100.com/blog/
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Just check more info from our blog. 
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: We only provide live chat software support there/ Thanks for stopping by. 
[Agent]: Operator Terry - Comm100 has left the chat.
