[Visitor]AYAZ: ı cant change my name when ı try to change this page is open ?
[Visitor]AYAZ: What can ı do ?
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hello AYAZ, this is Brian. How can I help you?
[Visitor]AYAZ: I cant change my name
[Visitor]AYAZ: when ı try to change it is same problem 
[Visitor]AYAZ: this page is opne ?=
[Visitor]AYAZ: what can ı do ?
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Have you cleared the caches? 
[Visitor]AYAZ: yes
[Visitor]AYAZ: ı can chatting now
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Okay 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: So what is the issue? 
[Visitor]AYAZ: but ıcant change my name ?
[Visitor]AYAZ: We are releasing Chatbot 1.1 & will be back shortly!

Date:	Friday, Aug.4, 2017
Time:	20:30 – 22:00 PDT
Duration:	1.5 hours
Expected Impact

During the release, online agents will be automatically logged out and the ongoing chats will be disrupted. Your chat button will show offline and your visitors can still leave messages.

If you have MaximumOn™ technology enabled in the account, we will switch your accounts to Secondary Server during the release. Your live chat will keep working. All visitor information and chat history will be synchronized.

Main Improvements in This Release

Chatbot now could access a database of customer-specific information, and provides personalized information to your customers. This means it can automatically handle a number of queries that previously, could only be handled by agents.

Some examples of customer questions you can now set up Chatbot to answer include:

What telephone number do you have on my record?
What is the tracking number for my order?
When is my next payment due?
[Visitor]AYAZ: When ı try to change ı see this page
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: No it is still the caches. 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: It is not all cleared. 
[Visitor]AYAZ: oke ı will try again to clear my history.
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Okay yes please 
[Visitor]AYAZ: thnak u
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: You are welcome ! 
