[Agent]Johnny - Comm100 (Training): Dear Support 6, thank you for contacting us! How may I help you?
[Visitor]Support 6: for just my chats, you have created two tickets. where can i going to see these tickets and its  reply ?
[Visitor]Support 6: no mail to  my accounts about these tickets
[Agent]Johnny - Comm100 (Training): Please stay with me 
[Agent]Johnny - Comm100 (Training): You will be contacted via email at  vanminh_1975*****yahoo.com
[Visitor]Support 6: yes, i asked because no email notify about this ticket
[Agent]Johnny - Comm100 (Training): You will be contacted as fast as possible at the same email vanminh_1975*****yahoo.com
