[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hi Tom, thank you for contacting Comm100. How can I help you?
[Visitor]Tom: how want to know more about comm100
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hi Tom, how are you today?
[Visitor]Tom: how can I customers it so that it will not carry comm100 live chat
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Here the step by step instructions, which show you how to customize the chat from start to finish: https://www.comm100.com/livechat/knowledgebase/get-started-with-comm100-live-chat.html
[Visitor]Tom: thanks
[Visitor]Tom: sorry one more question 
[Visitor]Tom: how many operators and chats can run at the same time for business plan
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Tom the Comm100 pricing is per agent license, one agent can handle up to as many chats as they like. 
[Visitor]Tom: ok so 49 usd for one agent
[Visitor]Tom: ?
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: That is correct, if you like I can have a sales agent get in touch with you and help you with your pricing needs.
[Visitor]: Ticket S10000-T557821 is created. The chat transcript will be attached to this ticket after the transcript is saved by system.
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
