[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hello DSIM Chat, this is Brian. How can I help you?
[Visitor]DSIM Chat: Good morning Brian!
[Visitor]DSIM Chat: Mamta this side
[Visitor]DSIM Chat: How are you? 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hi Mamta
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: I am good How are you
[Visitor]DSIM Chat: I am good
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: How can I help you today?
[Visitor]DSIM Chat: Today there is a webinar at 11.30pm (Indian time). 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Yes
[Visitor]DSIM Chat: Though I will not be in office, I would like to attend that, so just wanted to know if this webinar is on basic or there is something more apart form basic chat process
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Yes this webinar will be about our new feature.  The chatbot
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: It will not be the basic settings
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Actually the webinar will be recorded which you can check later if it is too late for your time today
[Visitor]DSIM Chat: Cool
[Visitor]DSIM Chat: No its ok, I will be at home and I remain awake till 230am which is afternoon for you might be :). Yes I have some other engagements but I will attend the webinar
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Okay sure. I am sure you will enjoy the webinar
[Visitor]DSIM Chat: I want live so that in case of any query I can ask questions then and there. 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Yes that is correct
[Visitor]DSIM Chat: Last time I watched the recorded one that you had sent me but later I eat your head with too many questions :P 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: :)
[Visitor]DSIM Chat: Therefore I want to attend this live session
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Okay no problem
[Visitor]DSIM Chat: Thank you so much brian. 
[Visitor]DSIM Chat: See you tomorrow after the demo. 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Thanks Mamta
[Visitor]DSIM Chat: I will share my experience with you and as usual if I dont understand anything or for any issues, I will catch you here. 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Sure, I look forward to hearing back from you
[Visitor]DSIM Chat: By the way will your chat option be available during the webinar? 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Yes live chat will carry on
[Visitor]DSIM Chat: Great. 
[Visitor]DSIM Chat: See you then
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: See you
[Visitor]DSIM Chat: Have a good day Brian
[Visitor]DSIM Chat: Bye for the day
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Bye now 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Take care ! 
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
