[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hello jenny, this is Brian. How can I help you?
[Visitor]jenny: Hi Brian
[Visitor]jenny: Good Morning
[Visitor]jenny: Terry is around ?
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hi Jenny, Terry will be in 3 hours or so. 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Is this still about the pricing questions ? 
[Visitor]jenny: No... i got the quote
[Visitor]jenny: i want extend my trial period 
[Visitor]jenny: is this possible ?
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Please hold on, let me see, for your enterprise account correct? 
[Visitor]jenny: Yes
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: One sec. 
[Visitor]jenny: sure
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hi Jenny, since your account manager will be Rob and he has the access for your account and can decide the extension for your account. So I will suggest you emailing him for this.  Is your trial currently closed?  If it is closed, I can help you to re-activate it , that is no problem. 
[Visitor]jenny: Ok thank you
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: You are welcome Jenny. 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hi Jenny, are we still connected? 
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hi, I haven't got any reply from you. It seems that you’re not available at the moment. I am going to leave this chat now. If you have any other questions, please feel free to try us again anytime. Bye for now and have a great day!
[Agent]: Operator Brian - Comm100 has left the chat.
