[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: Hi KRISHNA, this is Mellisa with Comm100. How may I help you today?
[Visitor]KRISHNA: I am confused about selecting branchfor my further studies
[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: I’m trying to help but you might have come to a wrong website. This is Comm100, a Canadian based customer service software company. Our website is www.comm100.com.
[Visitor]KRISHNA: I am getting IITHyd chem IITroorkee chem IITindore mech,ele so which branch should i opt for
[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: Krishna, we are a software company. You are at the wrong place for help.
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
