[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: Hi atan, this is Mellisa with Comm100. How may I help you today?
[Visitor]atan: Hello I have question regard's of spam
[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: Is it about the spam of email marketing solution?
[Visitor]atan: how to send directly to inbox not on spam.
[Visitor]atan: this is for taxation 
[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: Are you using our email marketing software, Atan?
[Visitor]atan: I'm using Thunderbird email. 
[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: If you are using Thunderbird, I would suggest you contact their support team.
[Visitor]atan: directly to Thunderbird support?
[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: Yes, please.
[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: This is the support line for Comm100 solution.
[Visitor]atan: okay and many thanks for your help Miss Mellisa.
[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: You are welcome.
[Agent]Mellisa -Comm100: Good luck and have a nice day!
