[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Hi Hans, this is Terry with Comm100. How may I help you today?
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Hi  Hans.
[Visitor]Hans: Hi, how are you? I would like to let you know, since yesterday I am getting this screen when I open the ticket system. I am using Firefox. Same issue wirh my MacBook using Firefox.
[Visitor]comm100.JPG: The visitor has sent a file: comm100.JPG
[Visitor]Hans: If I click ignore, your site is running
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: One end users uploaded some insecure file when replying to the our user ticket, which causes such alerts in some browser.  We have removed the relevant files from the system. Now we are waiting for Google to get alert removed. 
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Yes. you can ignore the  warning and continue to use the ticket system. 
[Visitor]Hans: Ok, Thanks. I was thinking to let you know it.
[Visitor]Hans: Have a nice day
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Appreciate your concern, Hans
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Have a good one!
[Visitor]Hans: you are always welcome
[Visitor]Hans: cheers
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
