[Agent]Hank-Comm100 (Training): Dear Gina, thank you for contacting us! How may I help you?
[Visitor]Gina: We're already using Comm100, and I would like to know the price for the ChatBot feature. I don't know who our account manager is, can you have that person contact us?
[Agent]Hank-Comm100 (Training): Hello, thanks for your interests in our product. ChatBot feature is just released, please contact our sales team for pricing.  Contact：sales*****comm100.com
[Visitor]Gina: thanks
[Agent]Hank-Comm100 (Training): You are very welcome.
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
