[Visitor]katrina: there were issues when we tried to use live chat today
[Visitor]katrina: was the system down?
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Hi katrina, this is Terry with Comm100. How may I help you today?
[Visitor]katrina: We had issues with live chat today
[Visitor]katrina: was there an issue on your side?
[Visitor]katrina: when we received calls, it was unresponsive so we couldnt answer the call
[Visitor]katrina: also when we tried to start achat windownit just buffered
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: May I know what issue you were facing?
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Any error message when you encountered the problem?
[Visitor]katrina: one agent received a message that said server exception
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: It might be temporary network issue on your side. Is everything all fine now?
[Visitor]katrina: im unsure
[Visitor]katrina: i will check now
[Visitor]katrina: can you please hold while i check
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Sure. Take your time. 
[Visitor]katrina: it seems to be working now
[Visitor]katrina: i couldnt get this live chat to work either so could have been an internet issue
[Visitor]katrina: we had more agents than usual using it, could that have slowed things down?
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: More agent to use the service will not effect the connection. 
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: We will keep monitoring our live chat and make sure it is running all fine. 
[Visitor]katrina: thats fine, thank you! i will be in cotnact with you again if it fails to work again
[Visitor]katrina: thanks for your help
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Sure, no problem. We are 24/7 online ;)
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Have a good one, Katrina.
[Agent]: Agent Terry - Comm100 has left the chat.
