[Visitor]Jensen Communities Live Support - Kim: I was registered for the Chatbot webinair yesterday and something came up and i was not able to attend.  Is there a way I can get information on how Chatbot works etc?
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hi Jensen Communities Live Support - Kim, thank you for contacting Comm100. How can I help you?
[Visitor]Jensen Communities Live Support - Kim: I was registered for the Chatbot webinair yesterday and something came up and i was not able to attend. Is there a way I can get information on how Chatbot works etc?
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Hi Jensen we will be having another Chatbot webinar next week again.
[Visitor]Jensen Communities Live Support - Kim: Ok...I will make sure that I sign up for it.  Do you happen to know what time?
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: I believe it will be at the same time and there will be an email going out to let you know the exact details.
[Visitor]Jensen Communities Live Support - Kim: thanks..I will keep an eye open for the email
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: excellent, was there anything else that I could help you with today?
[Visitor]Jensen Communities Live Support - Kim: that was all...thank you
[Agent]Paul - Comm100: Thank you for stopping by Comm100 and enjoy the rest of your day!
[Visitor]Jensen Communities Live Support - Kim: You too
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
