[Agent]Hank-Comm100 (Training): Dear Barinder kunar, thank you for contacting us! How may I help you?
[Visitor]Barinder kunar: Hii
[Visitor]: Operator Hank-Comm100 (Training) has turned on Auto Translation.
[Agent]Hank-Comm100 (Training): Hello,what can I help with you ?
[Visitor]Barinder kunar: I want to chat
[Agent]Hank-Comm100 (Training): Here is online technical support for Comm100 live chat product. Please let me know what problem do you have with our Comm100 live chat.
[Visitor]Barinder kunar: Is there any girl for chat
[Agent]Hank-Comm100 (Training): Hi, I’m trying to help but you might have come to a wrong website. This is Comm100, a live chat software provider. Our website is www.comm100.com. Is it possible that you confused us with another company?
[Visitor]Barinder kunar: I'm ask is any girl for chat
