[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hello Shlomo Shadmi  , this is Brian. How can I help you?
[Visitor]Shlomo Shadmi  : hi, the custom variable are the variables that hold the lead information and pass them to Salesforce?
[Visitor]Shlomo Shadmi  : not sure what it's for
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: The custom variables will be the ones which you can set so that the info about the user from your website can be mirrored to the live chat. 
[Visitor]Shlomo Shadmi  : when you say mirrored, you mean the back end, right?
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Actually no, I mean the info from your website ( about the user) can be pulled and reflected on to the agent console, this is what the customer variables will do. 
[Visitor]Shlomo Shadmi  : ok, I guess we meant the same thing... how can I set this up? I couldn't figure this out
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Here will be a help article about how to set the custom variables :  https://www.comm100.com/livechat/knowledgebase/how-to-set-custom-variable-value.html   some part of it will need your developers' help to finish 
[Visitor]Shlomo Shadmi  : wait, I didn't mean the info from the pre chat as we're not presenting forms... I mean that if I know the user from Salesforce, I want to be able to see their details in the agent console
[Visitor]Shlomo Shadmi  : is that what you meant?
[Visitor]Shlomo Shadmi  : or is it only what's in the cookie?
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Yes, that is exactly what custom variables can do.  As long as that info is available from your website, then it can be transferred to the agent console, we are not talking about the pre-chat here. 
[Visitor]Shlomo Shadmi  : when you say my website do you mean my crm?
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: yes correct 
[Visitor]Shlomo Shadmi  : ok, another thing - is it possible to make the chat box smaller?
[Visitor]Shlomo Shadmi  : it've very big on mobiles
[Visitor]Shlomo Shadmi  : and also in desktop
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Yes to change the chat window size, you can do it via custom CSS codes, which is under your chat window setting, and here will be a help article for that :  https://www.comm100.com/livechat/knowledgebase/customize-live-chat-window-with-css.html#ChangeChatWindowSize 
[Visitor]Shlomo Shadmi  : Amazing! thank you so much!!!
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: You are welcome ! 
