[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hello Siva, this is Brian. How can I help you?
[Visitor]Siva: Wet r u from
[Visitor]Siva: Wer
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Is this about Comm100? 
[Visitor]Siva: Comm 100 means
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Comm100 Live Chat is a real-time monitor and online chat tool. It helps you engage your customers in real time, increase your customer loyalty and increase sale revenue.
[Visitor]Siva: I want live video  chat. Can help u how to login to that web site
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hi, I’m trying to help but you might have come to a wrong website. This is Comm100, a live chat software provider. Our website is www.comm100.com. Is it possible that you confused us with another company?
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: It is not for live chatting, we sell live chat software here 
[Visitor]Siva: OK sorry sorry. K thank u
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Have a nice day 
[Visitor]Siva: Thank u brian
[Visitor]Siva: Same to u the same
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: bye
[Visitor]Siva: Bye
[Agent]: Operator Brian - Comm100 has left the chat.
