[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hello Cleopatra Mason, this is Norman with Comm100! How may I help you today?
[Visitor]Cleopatra Mason: Hi Team
[Visitor]Cleopatra Mason: I just wanted to confirm via the Keyword search, is there a way to search for more than one keyword at a time?
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Is it on the chat reports that you are trying to search the keywords?
[Visitor]Cleopatra Mason: I believe we have been able to locate it.
[Visitor]Cleopatra Mason: Thank you for your help!
[Visitor]Cleopatra Mason: Have a good day :)
[Visitor]: The visitor has left the chat.
