[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Hi OPD, this is Terry with Comm100. How may I help you today?
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Hi there
[Agent]Terry - Comm100: Hi, I haven't got any reply from you. It seems that you’re not available at the moment. I am going to leave this chat now. If you have any other questions, please feel free to try us again anytime. Bye for now and have a great day!
[Agent]: Agent Terry - Comm100 has left the chat.
