[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hello Will, this is Brian. How can I help you?
[Visitor]Will: Hi, I had an account and had not used it in a while but was trying to get in and can;t
[Visitor]Will: I clicked the password reset link and it didn't do anything
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Hi Will, what is the account email?  
[Visitor]Will: will*****gcit.net
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Please hold on, let me check. 
[Visitor]Will: thanks
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Will, when was the last time that you have successfully logged in?  And was it a free account? 
[Visitor]Will: it was free, its been about a year
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Yes that explained it.  We had a new policy for the free users since end of last year, the account will be closed and the data will be purged if the account has been dormant for over 6 months.   
[Visitor]Will: ah, that figures
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: Currently we cannot resume that old account,  you can register a new account with us.
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: As for if you can still get it freely,  it will need our product manager's help and she will reach out to you. 
[Visitor]Will: ok, that would be great
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: thanks will, sorry for the inconvenience. 
[Visitor]Will: no problem at all
[Agent]Brian - Comm100: thanks! 
