[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Hello Clement, this is Norman with Comm100! How may I help you today?
[Visitor]Clement: Hello Norman, I working for the french company Lexsi, we fight again cybercrime, especially against phishing. Its seems taht we have detected a fraudulent domain under your administration. Would you please confirm that the domain http://sgpbkbb.com/ is under your administration ? 
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: No it is not under our administration
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: May I know if you have any link on that website that forwards to us?
[Visitor]Clement: In fact the link is http://sgpbkbb.com/ and counterfeits the legitimate banking Group Societe Generale (http://www.privatebanking.societegenerale.co.uk). 
[Visitor]Clement: So it seems that we made a mistake in our database regarding the good contacts for the domain. Sorry for any inconvenience caused 
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: No worries! 
[Agent]Norman - Comm100: Thank you for contacting Comm 100 today!
Have a great day ahead!
[Agent]: Operator Norman - Comm100 has left the chat.
